Guide to the Rick Lazio Papers, 1981–2005
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series II. Congressional Papers
  - Legislation
    - Wage Issues/Concerns, Special Interest Groups, (National FED of The Blind, Bonus Issues, Sales Incentives, Film and TV Production), Sep-Oct 1999 (Box 83)
    - Work Opportunity Tax Credit, (Suggested Bill Language, Correspondence), Jun 1998-Sep 1999 (Box 83)
    - World Trade Association Disputes, (Ant-Biotics In Livestock Feed – Correspondence, International Anti-Dumping Measures), Jun-Nov 1999 (Box 83)
    - Bills/Appropriations Presented and Approved By R. Lazio, Jan-Oct 2000 (Box 83)
    - Breast and Cervical Cancer Treatment Act, (Statements, Press Releases Issued by R. Lazio, Pres. Bill Clinton), Oct 2000 (Box 83)
    - Breast Cancer, (Misc. Correspondence RE: Funding and Legislative Support), Dec 1992 - Nov 2000 (Box 83)
    - Correspondence, Congressional – Legislative/Appropriations, (Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio), Nov 1999 - Oct 2000; (3 folders) (Boxes 83, 84)
    - Energy, (Testimonies of R. Lazio RE: Energy Concerns, Environmental and Electricity Deregulation, Correspondence, Report, "Full Committee Restructuring Team," regarding Jurisdiction over Interstate Sale of Electricity), Aug 1999 - May 2000; (2 folders) (Box 84)
    - H.R. 21 Homeowner’s Insurance Availability Act, (Lazio Floor Statement, Report – Housing Bills Sponsored By R. Lazio, Correspondence, Press Releases), Mar-Aug 2000; (2 folders) (Box 84)
    - H.R. 1070 Briefing Book For Gov. George W. Bush, (The Breast and Cervical Cancer Treatment Act, Message and Description of Bill, Statistics, Bill Language, (Press Clippings, Cancer Statistics, The Breast and Cervical Cancer Treatment Act, Texas Statistics, Center For Disease Control Study), Feb-May 2000; (4 folders) (Box 84)
    - H.R. 1775 Amendment, South Shore Estuary, (Bill Language, Background Material), May 2000 (Box 84)
    - H.R. 2441 Fairness In Securities Transaction Act of 1999, (Subcommittee Mark-up Materials, Memoranda, Background Material, Correspondence, Lazio Statement, Congressional Budget Office Letter, Lazio Statement), Jun 1999 – Feb 2000; (3 folders) (Box 84)
    - H.R. 2944 Electricity Competition and Reliability Act, (Lazio Testimony, Background Information, Correspondence), Jun-Jul 2000 (Box 84)
    - H.R. 3308 Small Business Franchise Act, (Background Information, Correspondence), 2000 (Box 85)
    - H.R. 3313 Long Island Sound Restoration Act, (Lazio Floor Statement, Press Releases, Correspondence, Testimonies, Background Material, Bill Language), Nov 1999 - May 2000; (2 folders) (Box 85)
    - H.R. 3439 Radio Broadcasting Preservation Act, (Correspondence), Jan-Apr 2000 (Box 85)
    - H.R. 4807, Consumer Assurance of Radiologic Excellence Act, (Correspondence, Background Information, Hearing Questions, Talking Points), Mar-Jul 2000; (2 folders) (Box 85)
    - H.R. 4861 Clean Power Act, (Analysis, Bill Language), Jul 2000; (2 folders) (Box 85)
    - H.R. 4861 Syrian Nationals, Adjustment of Status, (Statement By Rick Lazio, Correspondence, Bill Language), Jun-Sep 2000 (Box 85)
    - H.R. 4920 Developmental Disabilities Act Reauthorization, (Memoranda, Correspondence, Lazio Statement, Notes, Draft Analysis, Amendments, Letters of Support, Senate and House Statements, Bill Summaries), Jun-Jul 2000; (3 folders) (Box 85)
    - H.R. 52 74, Consumer Assurance of Radiologic Excellence Act, (Correspondence, Bill Language), Mar-Sep 2000 (Box 85)
    - Health Care, (Correspondence (copies) to Pres. Clinton RE: Breast Cancer Treatment Act, Health Care Financing, Medicaid), Aug-Oct 2000 (Box 85)
    - Health Care, (Correspondence, Misc., Including Copies of Letters to Pres. Bill Clinton RE: Various Health Care Issues), Jun 1999 - Oct 2000 (Box 85)
    - Health Care, (Correspondence, Pres. Bill Clinton (copies) RE: Outpatient Pass Through Payments), Oct 2000 (Box 85)
    - Health Care, (Dept. of Health and Human Services Correspondence To Rick Lazio), May 1999 Oct 2000 (Box 85)
    - Health Care, (Federal Medical Assistance Percentage Notes, Memoranda, Bill Language), Jan 1999 - Jul 2000 (Box 85)
    - Health Care, (Health Care Financing Admin., Patient Access Preservation Act, Cancer Care—Background Material, Bill Language), 2000 (Box 85)
    - Health Care, (Medicaid, Correspondence and Bill Language Drafts), Oct 2000 (Box 86)
    - Health Care, Intergovernmental Transfer Payments, (NY Congressional Delegation Letter To Pres. Clinton, copy), 2 Aug 2000 (Box 86)
    - Health Care Financing Administration, (Medicare, Background Material and Correspondence To Sec. Dept. Health and Human Services), Jun-Aug 2000 (Box 86)
    - Home Heating Oil Crisis, (Press Releases, Photocopy of Letter To Pres. Clinton (1/25/2000), Background Material), Jan-Feb 2000 (Box 86)
    - Home Heating Oil Crisis, (Speech Text, Correspondence, Bill Language), Feb 2000 (Box 86)
    - Israel/Middle East/Palestinian Conflict, (Draft of Resolution Text), Jan 2000 (Box 86)
    - Puerto Rico, (Report On Lazio Voting Record), Jul 2000 (Box 86)
    - Reformulated Gas Hearing, (Statement by R. Lazio to Subcommittee on Health/Environment/Commerce), Mar 2000 (Box 86)
    - Roll Call Reports, 106th Congress, 7 Nov 2000; (6 folders) (Box 86)
  - Speech File
    - Misc. Introductions for Congressman Rick Lazio, undated (Box 87)
    - Supporting Material (For Visual Projection), undated; (3 folders) (Box 87)
    - Speeches, Talking Points, (Substance Abuse, Bay Shore Chamber of Commerce), Jul 1991-Nov 1992 (Boxes 87, 158)
    - Speeches, Aug-Nov 1993 (Box 87)
    - Speeches, (Includes Jokes Used For Edwin ‘Buzz’ Schwenk Roast (Suffolk County GOP Chairman), Aug-Dec 1993 (Box 87)
    - Speeches, (Includes "Stump Speech" With Notes), Feb-Nov 1994; (6 folders) (Box 87)
    - India Association of Long Island, Inc., Apr 1995 (Box 87)
    - Speeches, Jan-Dec 1995; (8 folders) (Box 88)
    - Speeches, Jan-Oct 1996; (4 folders) (Boxes 88, 89)
    - Assisted Suicide, (Lazio Statement On H.R. 1003, Assisted Suicide Funding Restriction Act), Mar 1997 (Box 89)
    - Egypt – Limits To U.S. Foreign Aid, (Speech Text, Drafts), 29 Jul 1997 (Box 89)
    - Freedom Alliance and Drug Court Speeches, (Speech Development Notes, Speech Text), Dec 1997 (Box 89)
    - Holocaust – Related Speeches By Rick Lazio, Jun 1997-Oct 1999 (Box 89)
    - Speeches, (Notes, Background Material), Feb-Dec 1997; (2 folders) (Box 89)
    - Trade-Related Speech Texts, (Includes Discussion Points For ‘Fast Track’ Votes, Press Clippings), Oct-Nov 1997 (Box 89)
    - Women’s Health Issues, Cancer, (Misc. Speeches), Oct 1997-Nov 1999; (2 folders) (Box 89)
    - Advances In Technology – Helping Young Children Grow, (Talking Points, Correspondence, Background Information), Nov-Dec 1998 (Box 89)
    - Financial Modernization/IMF Funding, (Speech Development Notes, Speech Text, Press Clippings), Mar-Jun 1998 (Box 89)
    - High Tech Task Force, Cancer Forum, (Speech Text, Talking Points), Aug-Sep 1998 (Box 89)
    - Housing/Home Ownership, (Talking Points, Press Clippings), Sep 1998 (Box 89)
    - Labor, Health, Human Services and Education Committee, (Lazio Statements RE: National Senior Service Corps, Apr 1998 (Box 89)
    - Lazio Speech Drafts, Budget, Welfare, Education, Crime, (Includes Research From Wirthlin Worldwide), May 1998 (Box 89)
    - Nassau-Suffolk Council of Hospital Auxiliaries, (Speech Text, Correspondence, Background Material), Jul-Nov 1998 (Box 89)
    - National Association For Medical Equipment Services, (Speech Text, Talking Points, Correspondence), Jan-Sep 1998 (Box 90)
    - National Association of Independent Insurers, (Interview/Taping, Talking Points, Sample Questions), 4 Mar 1998 (Box 90)
    - Nomination of JC Watts, Office of Chairman of House Republican Conference, (Speech Drafts, Correspondence, Notes, Background Material), 1998 (Box 90)
    - Presidential State of The Union Speech, (Lazio Talking Points, Media Strategy), Jan 1998 (Box 90)
    - Reference File For Speech Writing, (Includes West Babylon Republican Club Newsletter, Press Clippings, House Republican Conference Fact Sheet, "Conservatively Speaking" Booklet, 1998 (Box 90)
    - Reference Material – Credit Unions, (Talking Points), Jun-Aug 1998 (Box 90)
    - Reference Material – Health Care, Education, Tax Cuts, (Talking Points, Background Material), 1998 (Box 90)
    - Reference Material – Tax Burden, States, (Memoranda, Background Material), Apr 1998 (Box 90)
    - Reference Material – Veterans, Environment, Trial Lawyers, (Talking Points), Aug-Oct 1998 (Box 90)
    - Speeches, (Background Material, Memoranda, Notes RE: "Republican Message of Empowerment"), Feb-Dec 1998; (6 folders) (Box 90)
    - View From The Hill, National Cancer Institute, (Lazio Talking Points), 18 Sep 1997 (Box 91)
    - American Network of Community Options and Resources, (Talking Points, Correspondence, Background Material), Aug-Sep 1999 (Box 91)
    - Central Islip’s Brighter Future Has Begun, 30 Sep 1999 (Box 91)
    - Conservative Party Speeches, (Drafts With Handwritten Notes, Outlines, Remarks, Talking Points), 1999 (Box 91)
    - Housing, Taxes, Veterans – Memoranda, Correspondence, Material Used For Talking Points, Jul-Sep 1999 (Box 91)
    - International Relations, Misc. Legislation Addressed By R. Lazio, (Correspondence Used For Talking Points), Jun-Nov 1999 (Box 91)
    - Kidney Cancer Association, (Talking Points, Background Material), Jul 1999 (Box 91)
    - National Italian American Foundation, (Final Drafts), Oct 1999 (Box 91)
    - N.E.A., N.I.H., Tom Reynolds’ Government Day, Stump Speech (Including Critique), May 1999 (Box 91)
    - North Shore University Hospital, (Speech Text, Correspondence, Background Material), May 1999 (Box 91)
    - Speeches, May-Nov 1999; (2 folders) (Boxes 91, 158)
    - Speeches, (Draft Stump/Lincoln Day Speech (2/15/1999), Includes Notes), May-Nov 1999 (Boxes 91, 158)
    - Tax Reduction, Into of Gov. Pataki To House Com. On Government Reform, 15 Apr 1999 (Box 91)
    - Tom Delay Intro/NY State Conservative Party Reception, (Speech Text), 16 Nov 1999 (Box 91)
    - American Hotel and Motel Association, (Speech Text, Correspondence), Jan-Mar 2000 (Box 91)
    - Nomination of J.C. Watts, Chairman of The House Republican Conference), 2000 (Box 91)
    - West Islip High School, 43rd Commencement, 2000 (Box 91)
  - Subject File
    - Certificate, United Seniors Association, (Pro-Senior Tax Cut Award), undated (Box 92)
    - Report, The Language of the 21st Century, Luntz Research Companies, (Suggested National Communication Strategy For Congressional/Senatorial Candidates, undated; (3 folders) (Box 92)
    - The Best of The Good Clean Jokes, By Bob Phillips, (Paperback), 1989 (Box 92)
    - Biographical Reference File, (Resumes, Profiles, Who’s Who Entries, NY Times Article, 10/2/2005), 1990-2005 (Box 92)
    - Congressional Committees, (Reports, Correspondence, Notes, Background Material), Nov 1992; (2 folders) (Boxes 92, 158)
    - Hospital Mortgage Insurance Program, (Correspondence, Research Questions, Reports, Briefings, Presentations), Jun 1992-Oct 1997; (10 folders) (Boxes 92, 93)
    - Orientation Materials For Freshmen Congressional Members, (Correspondence, Resource Material, New Member-Elect Directory), Sep-Dec 1992; (2 folders) (Box 93)
    - Campaign Finance/Health Reform/Foreign Affairs/National Service, (Includes Form Letters For Constituent Correspondence, Reinventing Government/Congressional Reform/ NAFTA), 1993; (2 folders) (Box 93)
    - Clinton/Democrat Tax Bill and Suggested Arguments Against Bill, Aug 1993 (Box 93)
    - Missing Person Case – Annie McCarrick, (Lazio Speech Text/Talking Points RE: Northern Ireland, Correspondence, Background Material), 1993-1994; (2 folders) (Box 93)
    - NAFTRA, (Correspondence), Nov-Dec 1993 (Box 93)
    - National Republican Congressional Committee, (List Exchange Agreement), Dec 1993 (Box 93)
    - Op-Ed Articles By Rick Lazio, (Including Misc. Articles, Medicare, Arts, NAFTRA, Saddam Hussein), Apr 1993-Nov 1997 (Box 93)
    - Programs, Misc. Events, Dinners, Fundraisers, 1993-1995 (Box 94)
    - Republican Freshman Fly-In, Freshman Class Event Packet, Oct 1993 (Box 94)
    - Staff Memos To R. Lazio, Jan 1993-Feb 1994 (Box 94)
    - Vote Tally/Ratings Reports, (Published by Misc. Special Interest Groups), 1993-1994; (9 folders) (Boxes 94, 115 (Oversize))
    - Voting Record Report (for Rep. Rick Lazio), (newsletter photocopies) - [see Printed Material, 1993-1999 for originals] (Box 158)
    - Affordable Housing, (Report, Center On Budget and Policy Priorities…7/1995…Background Material, Interview With R. Lazio, "A Conversation With Chairman of The Housing Subcommittee"), Jan 1994-Jul 1995 (Box 95)
    - Daily Schedule For Rick Lazio, May-Dec 1994 (Box 95)
    - Fire Island Association, (Correspondence, Press Clippings), Mar-Sep 1994 (Box 95)
    - National Republican Congressional Committee Issues Council, (Correspondence), Aug 1994 (Box 95)
    - National Republican Congressional Committee, (Political Report (1/17/94), Capabilities and Services Report 95/96, Correspondence, Fundraising Talking Points), 1994; (2 folders) (Box 95)
    - National Taxpayers Union Foundation, (Correspondence), Jul-Sep 1994 (Box 95)
    - Office Manual For Lazio Office, 1 Jan 1994 (Box 95)
    - PACs – Potential Contacts, (Correspondence), Feb 1995-Jul 1995; (2 folders) (Box 95)
    - Political Action Committee, (Correspondence, Mailing Lists), Feb-Oct 1994 (Box 95)
    - Press Clippings, Crime Bill Coverage, Aug 1994 (Boxes 95, 158)
    - Questionnaires Sent To Rick Lazio, Aug-Sep 1994 (Box 96)
    - Questionnaire, Suffolk Life Congressional Candidate Questionnaire, Oct 1994 (Boxes 96, 158)
    - Report, H.U.D. Restructuring/Dismantling, Dec 1994; (2 folders) (Box 96)
    - Republican Budget Initiative, F.Y., 1995 (Box 96)
    - Right To Life and Conservative Party, (Acceptance Forms, Designation For Nomination Signed By Rick Lazio), 27 Jun 1994 (Box 96)
    - Budget Review Reports, Clinton Admin., Aug 1995-Feb 1997 (Box 96)
    - Conservative Party, (Newsletters, Correspondence, Press Clippings), Dec 1995-Sep 1996 (Box 96)
    - Housing, Correspondence From Constituents and Special Interest Groups, Jan 1995 – Jul 1996; (3 folders) (Box 96)
    - H.U.D./Housing Issues, (Memoranda, Correspondence…Includes Lazio Essay, ‘Putting Our House Indoor,’, 1995-1996 (Box 96)
    - Legislative Profile For R. Lazio, 4 Jan 1995 - 28 Oct 1996 (Box 96)
    - NEA, American Symphony Orchestra, (Briefing and Background, Talking Points), Jun 1997 (Box 96)
    - NEA, (Correspondence To R. Lazio RE: Thanks For Support of NEA, Includes Letters From Young Adults, City Kids Foundation, Correspondence To/From R. Lazio and NEA Officials), Jan 1995-Jul 1998; (4 folders) (Box 97)
    - NEA, (Op-Ed Articles By R. Lazio…Includes OP-Ed On ‘The Meaning of the 4th of July’), Apr 1997-May 1998 (Box 97)
    - NEA, (Press Clippings, Featuring R. Lazio…Includes Lazio NEA Chronology of Events), Feb-Jul 1997 (Box 97)
    - NEA, (Press Release Draft, NEH Grant List), Jun-Jul 1998 (Box 97)
    - NEA, (Speech Texts, Including ‘A Bipartisan Defense of the Arts’), Apr-Jul 1998 (Box 97)
    - Report, Opportunities For Terminating, Consolidating…, (HUD Programs), Jan 1995; (2 folders) (Box 97)
    - Republican National Committee, (Correspondence, Memoranda), Jan 1995 – Feb 1996 (Box 97)
    - Voting Record/Tally Publications, 1995-1996; (7 folders) (Boxes 97, 115 (Oversize), 158)
    - Cold War Report For Press Conference, (Preparation RE: Introduction of ‘Concurrent Resolution’), Apr 1996; (2 folders) (Box 98)
    - Congressional Working Group On Cancer, (Correspondence, Press Clippings), Nov 1996-May 1998 (Box 98)
    - Travel Disclosure - David Horne, 1996-1998 (Box 162)
    - Daily Schedule For Rick Lazio, Nov 1996-Nov 1997 (Box 98)
    - Dynalantic Corp – Federal Contract, (Correspondence), Oct 1996-Dec 1997 (Box 98)
    - Federal Housing Administration/Hospital Mortgage Insurance, (Correspondence, Background Material), Nov 1996-Oct 1998; (2 folders) (Box 98)
    - National Republican Congressional Committee, (Press Releases, Correspondence, Report On Summer 1995 Meeting), Jan-Feb 1996 (Box 98)
    - Pledge Requests From Misc. Special Interest Groups, 1996 (Box 98)
    - Questionnaires Sent To Rick Lazio, Sep-Oct 1996 (Box 98)
    - Senior Month, (Correspondence, Strategy For R.L. Senior Center Visits), Feb-3 1996 (Box 98)
    - Special Interest Groups, (Italian, Teachers, Christian, Hispanic, Jewish…Correspondence, Background Material), 1996 (Box 98)
    - Veteran’s Affairs, (Correspondence, Lazio Newsletter), Feb 1996-Aug 1997 (Box 158)
    - Women’s Health, Cancer, (Correspondence, Memoranda, Bill Language), Jul 1996 - Mar 2000 (Box 98)
    - 2nd Congressional District, NY, (Project Proposals, Correspondence), Nov-Dec 1997 (Box 99)
    - Accomplishments of R. Lazio For 1997, (List of Legislative Involvement) (Box 99)
    - American Counseling Association, (Correspondence, Background Material), Aug 1997-Jan 1999 (Box 99)
    - Assisi, Italy – Fresco Repair, Earthquake Assistance, (Letter of Support), Oct 1997 (Box 99)
    - Babylon, Long Island, Train Station Improvements, (Correspondence), Nov 1997 (Box 99)
    - Bay Shore Long Island Aquarium, (Correspondence, Press Clippings), Aug-Nov 1997; (2 folders) (Box 99)
    - Cancer Awareness, (Correspondence From R. Lazio RE: Cancer Awareness Briefing, Talking Points, 5/18/1998), Oct 1997-Jan 1998 (Box 99)
    - Census Report, Population and Housing, District 2, 1997 (Box 99)
    - Central Islip, Courthouse Construction Project, (Correspondence), Nov 1993-Apr 1997 (Box 99)
    - Community Services Block Grant, (Background Material, Notes), 1997 (Box 99)
    - Daily Schedule For Rick Lazio, Nov 1997-Aug 1999 (Box 99)
    - Egypt/State Dept, (Letter From Egyptian Ambassador, Talking Points (Pan Am 103, Cairo Summit, Arafat…), Aug 1997 (Box 99)
    - Environmental Accomplishments By Rick Lazio – Key Environmental Votes, 1997 (Box 99)
    - Housing, (Correspondence, Congressional To/From R. Lazio), Apr 1997-Apr 1998 (Box 99)
    - Housing – Funding Requests, (Correspondence), Feb 1997-Jan 1998 (Box 99)
    - Housing – Manufactured Housing Institute, (Correspondence), Mar 1997-Feb 1998 (Box 99)
    - Housing/Settlement Housing Fund, (Lazio Statements, Correspondence), Feb-May 1997 (Box 99)
    - Ireland – Agreement Reached In The Multi-Party Negotiations, (Correspondence From Ireland’s Ambassador, Agreement Text), Apr 1998 (Box 99)
    - Ireland – Deportation, (Statement By Rick Lazio 5/14/1997, Correspondence), Feb 1997 - Aug 2000 (Box 99)
    - Ireland – Human Rights Issues, (Correspondence), Oct 1997 - Jul 2000 (Box 100)
    - Ireland – Legislation (misc.) Regarding Ireland, (Includes Lazio Statement on Ireland, Correspondence), Mar 1997 - Oct 2000 (Box 100)
    - Ireland – Memoranda, Correspondence (misc.), Feb 1997-May 1999 (Box 100)
    - Ireland – Northern Ireland Alert, (Congressional Score Cards), Sep 1997 - Sep 2000 (Box 100)
    - Ireland – Northern Ireland Visa For Peace and Reconciliation, (Correspondence, Summary of Bill, Bill Language), Jul 1998 (Box 100)
    - Ireland – Quinn, Paul, Endorsement For Ambassadorship To Ireland, (Correspondence), Feb 1998-May 1998 (Box 100)
    - Ireland – Statements By Rick Lazio, Jan 1997 - Aug 2000 (Box 100)
    - Italian Ambassador Recommendation – Tom Foglieita, (Includes Talking Points For Salleo Reception), Jan-Feb 1997 (Box 100)
    - Jubilee 2000, New Millennium Christian Celebration, (Memoranda, Correspondence), Aug 1997-Feb 1998 (Box 100)
    - Letters of Recognition, Awards From Various Interest Groups, (Includes Award From The Seniors Coalition), Nov 1997 - Oct 2000 (Box 100)
    - Main Street Republican Partnership, (Mission Statement, Communications Plan, Quotes, Finance, Research, Media Kit), 1997-1998 (Box 100)
    - Main Street Republican Partnership, (Briefing Book), 1997-1998 (Box 100)
    - Main Street Republican Partnership, (By-Laws, Org. Action, Certificate of Secretary, Draft Mission Statements, Policy Proposals), 1997-1998 (Box 100)
    - Main Street Republican Partnership, (Meeting Notes), 1997-1998 (Box 100)
    - Main Street Republican Partnership, (Briefing Book, 10/7/1997 – Financial Report, Policy Agenda, Recruitment, Accomplishments), 1997-1998 (Box 100)
    - Main Street Republican Partnership, (Correspondence), Feb-Oct 1997; (2 folders) (Box 100)
    - Main Street Republican Partnership, (Press Clippings), Feb 1997-Oct 1998 (Box 101)
    - Main Street Republican Partnership, (Project Updates, Drafts of Exec. Summary, Mission Statements, Strategic Plans), Apr 1997-Apr 1998 (Box 101)
    - Main Street Republican Partnership, (Mission Statement, Talking Points, Agendas, Strategic and Communications Plans), Feb 1997-Jan 1998 (Box 101)
    - Main Street Republican Partnership (Coalition), (Briefing Booklets), Jul-Aug 1997 (Box 101)
    - Main Street Republican Partnership, (Board Meeting Briefing Booklet), 11 Feb 1998; (2 folders) (Boxes 101, 158)
    - Main Street Republican Partnership, (Meeting Minutes, Agenda, Talking Points, Time Table), Feb-Nov 1998 (Box 101)
    - Main Street Republican Partnership, (Correspondence), Feb 1998-Dec 1998 (Box 101)
    - Main Street Republican Partnership, (Board Meeting Briefing Booklet), 10 Jun 1998 (Box 101)
    - Main Street Republican Partnership, (Business Breakfast Briefing, Lazio Speech Text, Issue Papers, Background Information), Sep 1998 (Box 101)
    - Main Street Republican Partnership, (Board of Directors Mtg. Booklet), 5 Oct 1998 (Box 101)
    - Main Street Republican Partnership, (Lazio Financing Briefing Booklet, Mission Statement, Policy Agenda), Oct 1998 (Box 101)
    - Main Street Republican Partnership, (Executive Board Mtg. Briefing Book), 8 Dec 1998 (Box 102)
    - Main Street Republican Partnership, (Agenda Conference, 10/28/1997 – Talking Points, Mission Statement, Quotes, Draft Materials, 12/1997), 1997-1998 (Box 102)
    - "National Policy Approaches to the Lack of Available Homeowners Insurance in Disaster-Prone Areas", (Lazio Speech Drafts, Correspondence, Hearing Summary, Lazio Editorial, Research Material), Jun-Sep 1997; (3 folders) (Box 102)
    - National Sea Grant College Program, (Correspondence, Floor Remarks), Mar-Jun 1997 (Box 102)
    - NATO – Clinton, Bill, (Correspondence RE: NATO Enlargement), 11 Sep 1997 (Box 102)
    - Navy EA-6B Electronic Warfare Aircraft, (Correspondence From Pres. Bill Clinton (12/17/1993) and Sen. Alfonse D’Amato (7/26/1994), 1997 (Box 102)
    - NEA, (Press Clippings, Lazio Statement and Press Release), Apr-Jul 1997 (Box 102)
    - New York Bankers Association/Insurance Agreement, (Correspondence, Press Release), Sep 1997 (Box 102)
    - New York State Federal Priorities Report From Office of Gov. George Pataki, Feb 1997 (Box 102)
    - Northrop Grumman Joint Stars Aircraft, (Correspondence), Nov 1997 (Box 102)
    - Op-Ed, Balanced Budget/Senior Citizens, (Drafts, Correspondence, Background and Research Material), Jun 1997 (Box 102)
    - Op-Ed, Homeowners Insurance, St. Petersburg Times, 26 Aug 1997 (Box 102)
    - Op-Ed, Housing and Poverty, Washington Times, (Drafts, Comments, Correspondence), 9 Jul 1997 (Box 102)
    - Op-Ed, Saddam Hussein, Daily News, (Includes Letter To Publisher of Suffolk Life Newspaper RE: Inaccuracies Printed Regarding Running With Gov. Pataki), 28 Nov 1997 (Box 102)
    - Presidential Inauguration, (Invitations and Letters To R. Lazio Requesting Invitations), 1997 (Box 102)
    - Press Clippings, Welfare Articles, Jun-Dec 1997; (2 folders) (Boxes 103, 158)
    - Retlif Testing Laboratories, (Correspondence), Feb 1997 (Box 103)
    - Seahawk Helicopters, (Export License, Correspondence), Apr-Jun 1997 (Box 103)